So here is a kit that you could do all on your own, that we sell as a complete kit.
When you get this kit, you can start cutting mats the moment you unwrap it.
Remember the mat guide that we had?
We have a mat guide.
The tape measure, remember you want to use a good tape measure to measure for your mats.
Then we have a straight edge.
We are going to show you how to use this Alco straight cutter to cut all of your mats.
You can cut the opening and you can cut those designs (like little ducks and balloons) in the matting.
When you want to cut your mat down to size, we have a Stanley knife; the best that you want to use.
We have a straight edge.
Now, this straight edge is not to measure with, remember.
It's so that you can cut your own mats with the Alco mat razor.
We have a clamp that will clamp this to your table.
We give you pencils.
You want to use a good quality pencil and keep it very sharp.
Then we give you tracing paper; a whole book of tracing paper.
Remember, you could trace that little duck on the actual picture and then cut it into the matting.
Then we are going to give you different templates that you can cut in your matting; all different kinds (feathers, leaves...).
Then, remember when we put the two mats together?
This is your double stick tape that is going to connect your double mat together.
We have a razor blade that once you cut your opening, if it doesn't fall out, you are going to need a little razor blade to cut that corner.
So, we wanted to provide every single thing that you need to cut your mats.
We give you twenty eleven by fourteen mat boards that you can use to remember your favorite eight by ten picture of your cat or your kids or a landscape.
You can use these and cut for your own pictures, right there on the very first day that you get it.
So, this kit will help you to design and cut your own special mats.